{
    "subject": "resource/Kip_Moore",
    "predicate": "ontology/instrument",
    "object": "resource/Guitar",
    "human_readable": "Kip Moore plays the Guitar.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9603272080421448,
            "question": "What kind of music does Kip Moore play that involves the guitar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9480464458465576,
            "question": "Does Kip Moore use a guitar in his performances?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9310685992240906,
            "question": "What instrument does Kip Moore play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9301207065582275,
            "question": "How proficient is Kip Moore at playing the guitar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9132091999053955,
            "question": "Is Kip Moore a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8918356895446777,
            "question": "Is the guitar a central element in Kip Moore's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8529602289199829,
            "question": "Which musical instrument is associated with Kip Moore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7644850015640259,
            "question": "Has Kip Moore ever released songs featuring guitar solos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7592518925666809,
            "question": "What is Kip Moore known for playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6281180381774902,
            "question": "What musical skills does Kip Moore possess?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kip Moore plays the Guitar.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3494_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Kip Moore known for playing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3494_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Kip Moore ever released songs featuring guitar solos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3494_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which musical instrument is associated with Kip Moore?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3494_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3494_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3494_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3494_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3494_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3494_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3494_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3494_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3494_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3494_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3494_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Kip Moore has a song called \"Guitar Man\", and in one of the texts, it's stated that Moore says \"I'll play 'em fast, I'll play 'em slow, I'm the guitar man.\" This suggests that Moore plays the guitar."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Kip Moore plays the Guitar.\" For instance, multiple sources mention his involvement with guitars and music early in life and even during performances. Specifically, document 39.txt mentions him strumming a guitar on golf road trips, and other documents refer to his solo acoustic performance of \u201cGuitar Man.\u201d"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}